<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Bunnesite</title>
    <link>https://ladybunne.net/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Bunnesite</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 22:18:00 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ladybunne.net/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Rainy Tuesday</title>
      <link>https://ladybunne.net/rainy-tuesday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 22:18:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ladybunne.net/rainy-tuesday/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi again. It&amp;rsquo;s been a little while. A busy week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s a little run-down of how my various pursuits have been.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;final-fantasy-xiv&#34;&gt;Final Fantasy XIV&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Things with all my various raid groups are going well enough. I have:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pyretic&lt;/strong&gt;, my Savage static, who are just about BiS. No definite plans after that.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blue Fire&lt;/strong&gt;, my serious BLU static, who have just cleared O8S and are now starting on O12S. They&amp;rsquo;ve cleared all the morbol raids, so O12S is their last &amp;ldquo;hard&amp;rdquo; fight before they&amp;rsquo;re done!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pilot Lights&lt;/strong&gt;, my casual BLU static. They&amp;rsquo;re making good progress, surprisingly so for a less serious group, but unfortunately they got stuck on T13 today. Once they clear it they have A12S and A8S left.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m idly planning on doing some more work on solo Palace things eventually, as well as trying to hit Crystal in PvP. Neither are immediate goals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://discord.gg/thefireplace&#34;&gt;The Fire Place&lt;/a&gt;, the Materia hub community I run, is doing well - we&amp;rsquo;re at almost 1700 members now. We&amp;rsquo;ve got a fun blue mage Crystal Tower event planned on the weekend, which should be fun. BA runs within the server have also been going well - nothing more than frag runs, but they&amp;rsquo;re successful and generally fun enough to run.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Housing&amp;rsquo;s being fixed in a week, I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to having a large to play with again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been really enjoying some of my glams lately, too. I&amp;rsquo;d like to get back to 3d modelling when I have time, but&amp;hellip; who has time?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;other-games&#34;&gt;Other games&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve finally stopped playing OSRS, for now. I really don&amp;rsquo;t have time for a second MMO. It was fun, but also very tedious. I&amp;rsquo;ll likely go back to it during a patch lull sometime.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;which brings me to my next point - I&amp;rsquo;ve been getting into Monster Hunter Rise with some close friends (whoops). It&amp;rsquo;s been a very fun, enjoyable time. I&amp;rsquo;m having a lot of fun with the greatsword, which is a slow, super-powered weapon that requires a lot of precision and good timing. It&amp;rsquo;s very punishing if you mess it up, so&amp;hellip; in a way, that&amp;rsquo;s good, too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m playing through Outer Wilds (the best game ever) with my parents. Mum&amp;rsquo;s making good progress with it, Dad&amp;rsquo;s just about to leave Timber Hearth. It&amp;rsquo;s been really fun and I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to seeing how they both progress, especially how their runs diverge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;personal&#34;&gt;Personal&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve got another housing inspection this Friday. Here&amp;rsquo;s hoping nothing weird happens with it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also have some errands I&amp;rsquo;ve been putting off, mostly some paperwork I need to process and likely store somewhere. Truly, staying on top of everything is an impossible task.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mood things have been fine, I suppose. Up and down, as is to be expected, but overall nothing too terrible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have a job interview that&amp;rsquo;s sort of happening in the background. It&amp;rsquo;s been long and drawn-out over weeks at this point, which is&amp;hellip; not ideal, but it is what it is. It&amp;rsquo;s for dev work, which would be nice to get back into. I&amp;rsquo;m somewhere between apathetic at More Job Stuff, and cautiously optimistic that it could actually be great. So it goes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope your week&amp;rsquo;s been good so far. Thanks for reading.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Ladybunne&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloudy Monday</title>
      <link>https://ladybunne.net/cloudy-monday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 17:18:15 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ladybunne.net/cloudy-monday/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s a pretty cloudy Monday today. I had a property valuation this morning - a valuer came out to take some pictures of my apartment. I&amp;rsquo;m hoping this doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean my landlord is intending to sell, because that would mean I&amp;rsquo;d have to move out, and I &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; don&amp;rsquo;t want to do that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But it was otherwise painless! My vacuum broke about half an hour before the valuer arrived, which was a hassle. I&amp;rsquo;ll have to see if I can put it back together at some point.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking a lot about what sorts of things I want to write here. I&amp;rsquo;ve set myself two rules - be honest, and no deleting. That&amp;rsquo;s hard, because I don&amp;rsquo;t really want to leave a public trail of things that anyone can just come and learn about me&amp;hellip; but, maybe I should be less afraid of that. I think the alternative is kind of sad - who wants to look back and see 30 years of deleted memories?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, here I am. Trying to use this site to be a bit more outspoken about myself. I&amp;rsquo;m intentionally using this instead of, say, Twitter or another algorithm-riddled site. It&amp;rsquo;s a bit more &amp;ldquo;pure&amp;rdquo;, and less engineered to grab/hold attention. This is just me expressing myself&amp;hellip; shouting into the void and seeing what happens.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ll likely work on the format of this over time. I used to have a site that had both &amp;ldquo;posts&amp;rdquo; (long-form blog posts like this one) and &amp;ldquo;microposts&amp;rdquo; (like tweets but not on Twitter), and that worked well. I&amp;rsquo;ll see if I get around to adding that functionality in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Otherwise, we&amp;rsquo;ll see how this whole site thing holds up. Fingers crossed it works out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Ladybunne&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro</title>
      <link>https://ladybunne.net/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 21:12:29 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ladybunne.net/intro/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi. I&amp;rsquo;m Ladybunne, and this is my site. I&amp;rsquo;ve been meaning to remake this for quite some time. Sorry it&amp;rsquo;s taken so long.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope I didn&amp;rsquo;t keep you waiting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t have much to say right now. I need to set the site up and get it working properly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Talk to you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Ladybunne&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
