<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bunnesite</title>
    <link>https://ladybunne.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Bunnesite</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 21:40:07 +1100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ladybunne.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Flicker</title>
      <link>https://ladybunne.net/flicker/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 21:40:07 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ladybunne.net/flicker/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;quot;&amp;hellip;where once there burned a bright blaze, the pyre of a vibrant, empassioned soul, there now stood a faint flicker. The occasional glance revealed naught but a softly glowing coal&amp;hellip; only observant eyes, watching, would spot a small surge, every so often.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;This was what remained of her. Brought low by the adversities of life, drained of what used to make her crackle with warmth, with fierce devotion. An endless torrent of dampening oppression, progressively eroded at her fire, her very being.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;She cried out, silently, as her essence was torn from her, reduced to nothing but embers, ash and steam. Her refusal meant nothing before the whims of those stifling influences. By now she was beyond saving.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;As her fleeting life force drained, day by day, she reflected on days gone past, times when she was much more of herself. Those memories were all she had now.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip;for a spent flame has no future.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Silence</title>
      <link>https://ladybunne.net/silence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 19:40:18 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ladybunne.net/silence/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what&#34;&gt;What&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All the words of a lifetime and it&amp;rsquo;s impossible to pick the right ones. Hi.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In response to recent changes in my demeanour and behaviour as of late, a number of people have been increasingly asking me &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;what&amp;rsquo;s wrong&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;, or offering sentiments along the lines of &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;here if you need to talk&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;. It&amp;rsquo;s emotionally difficult for me to respond to either, so I&amp;rsquo;m writing here in the hopes that I can simply show people this, and have it speak for me. I&amp;rsquo;ll try and keep it as brief as I can.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m not okay.&lt;/strong&gt; I haven&amp;rsquo;t been for a long time. If you&amp;rsquo;re close to me you would have known some of the issues that have plagued me over the last few years, or even more specifically, during the first half of 2022. If not, it&amp;rsquo;s not worth getting into. Things have gotten a lot worse as of late, escalating to a point where not a single day goes by without a lot of crying. I&amp;rsquo;ve started withdrawing from everything and everyone&amp;hellip; I just don&amp;rsquo;t have the energy to put on a smile, these days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;why&#34;&gt;Why&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time and time again I have been subject to abuse, harassment, heartbreak and manipulation, in my social endeavours this year, from so very many sources. An unfortunate side-effect of being a very visible, very public person in XIV circles, I suppose. I have thick skin, but everyone has their limits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After everything that&amp;rsquo;s happened to me this year, I&amp;rsquo;ve had my hopes of happiness progressively eroded away. I&amp;rsquo;ve rebuilt them after each setback, tried to pick myself up, but this time I have nothing left. I went into this year with a lot of optimism, and it&amp;rsquo;s all gone. I&amp;rsquo;ve been pushed to the point where I need therapy, soon, or there may not be much left of me before long.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We live in a world where marginalised groups have systemic violence committed against them on the daily. We are expected to live in spite of that. We are expected to tell our stories, to educate those around us, to bridge the gap between society&amp;rsquo;s violence and society&amp;rsquo;s curiosity. I am sick and tired of having to explain to the world what a &amp;ldquo;transgender person&amp;rdquo; is. I&amp;rsquo;m tired of paying trans tax. Of the ensuing loneliness, the judgement, the double standards, the ever-ensuing onslaught of obstacles we&amp;rsquo;re forced to overcome in order to simply &lt;em&gt;live.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every day that goes by, I feel more and more like this world is one I was never meant to live in. It feels cruel, unyielding, ambivalent to people on the fringe. I&amp;rsquo;m tired of having to wake up every day and battle through that, just to perpetuate an existence that causes me endless agony. Why would &lt;em&gt;anyone&lt;/em&gt; continue to subject themselves to such a living? It&amp;rsquo;s insanity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-now&#34;&gt;What Now?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t know. There&amp;rsquo;s not much anyone can do for me at this point. I&amp;rsquo;m trying to find a therapist, but wait times for them are seeming infeasible. I&amp;rsquo;m also trying to keep myself together, but I can feel things slipping, I can feel myself falling apart.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For once I don&amp;rsquo;t have the answers here. I don&amp;rsquo;t know what I need. I don&amp;rsquo;t know how to solve these problems. Nothing scares me more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If I could ask one thing&amp;hellip; please try and build a better world for people like me, for people who are worse off than me, people who are less resilient than me. I don&amp;rsquo;t think my story&amp;rsquo;s going to have a happy ending - a person can only endure so much pain before they break.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope that those who come after me get to have happy endings to their stories.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fatigue Friday</title>
      <link>https://ladybunne.net/fatigue-friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 21:37:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ladybunne.net/fatigue-friday/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;May&amp;rsquo;s been busy. It feels like it&amp;rsquo;s getting harder and harder to take a moment to myself and write these.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Between voting, inspections, cleaning, interviews and running everything I run, a lot of my energy has just been burned through. The rest of my time has been spent either trying to write code, which is an ordeal at times, or trying to invest in some self-care, which has had mixed results.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;XIV&amp;rsquo;s been a lot less fun lately. Outside of blue mage raiding I&amp;rsquo;ve had little desire to log in. Everything feels a lot harder than it should. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t feel like burnout, it just feels like the game is, currently, less enjoyable. I don&amp;rsquo;t know how to feel about that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I feel like I&amp;rsquo;m approaching the end of my time in Monster Hunter, for now at least. It&amp;rsquo;s been really fun and I&amp;rsquo;ve done pretty well, but myself and my friends are all getting a bit tired of it, too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been messing around with a game called Bitburner that&amp;rsquo;s a fun combination of idle game and programming environment. You write scripts that (ideally) automate the boring parts of the game away, leaving you with an efficiency suite you can then iterate on and improve as you go. It is, at the very least, getting me to write more code, more often.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I feel pretty misunderstood a lot of the time, I think, even from some people I&amp;rsquo;d consider close or friends at times. It&amp;rsquo;s starting to wear me down.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hopefully things are better by the next time I write a post. I might have a job by then.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Rainy Tuesday</title>
      <link>https://ladybunne.net/rainy-tuesday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 22:18:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ladybunne.net/rainy-tuesday/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi again. It&amp;rsquo;s been a little while. A busy week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s a little run-down of how my various pursuits have been.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;final-fantasy-xiv&#34;&gt;Final Fantasy XIV&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Things with all my various raid groups are going well enough. I have:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pyretic&lt;/strong&gt;, my Savage static, who are just about BiS. No definite plans after that.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blue Fire&lt;/strong&gt;, my serious BLU static, who have just cleared O8S and are now starting on O12S. They&amp;rsquo;ve cleared all the morbol raids, so O12S is their last &amp;ldquo;hard&amp;rdquo; fight before they&amp;rsquo;re done!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pilot Lights&lt;/strong&gt;, my casual BLU static. They&amp;rsquo;re making good progress, surprisingly so for a less serious group, but unfortunately they got stuck on T13 today. Once they clear it they have A12S and A8S left.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m idly planning on doing some more work on solo Palace things eventually, as well as trying to hit Crystal in PvP. Neither are immediate goals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://discord.gg/thefireplace&#34;&gt;The Fire Place&lt;/a&gt;, the Materia hub community I run, is doing well - we&amp;rsquo;re at almost 1700 members now. We&amp;rsquo;ve got a fun blue mage Crystal Tower event planned on the weekend, which should be fun. BA runs within the server have also been going well - nothing more than frag runs, but they&amp;rsquo;re successful and generally fun enough to run.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Housing&amp;rsquo;s being fixed in a week, I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to having a large to play with again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been really enjoying some of my glams lately, too. I&amp;rsquo;d like to get back to 3d modelling when I have time, but&amp;hellip; who has time?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;other-games&#34;&gt;Other games&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve finally stopped playing OSRS, for now. I really don&amp;rsquo;t have time for a second MMO. It was fun, but also very tedious. I&amp;rsquo;ll likely go back to it during a patch lull sometime.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;which brings me to my next point - I&amp;rsquo;ve been getting into Monster Hunter Rise with some close friends (whoops). It&amp;rsquo;s been a very fun, enjoyable time. I&amp;rsquo;m having a lot of fun with the greatsword, which is a slow, super-powered weapon that requires a lot of precision and good timing. It&amp;rsquo;s very punishing if you mess it up, so&amp;hellip; in a way, that&amp;rsquo;s good, too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m playing through Outer Wilds (the best game ever) with my parents. Mum&amp;rsquo;s making good progress with it, Dad&amp;rsquo;s just about to leave Timber Hearth. It&amp;rsquo;s been really fun and I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to seeing how they both progress, especially how their runs diverge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;personal&#34;&gt;Personal&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve got another housing inspection this Friday. Here&amp;rsquo;s hoping nothing weird happens with it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also have some errands I&amp;rsquo;ve been putting off, mostly some paperwork I need to process and likely store somewhere. Truly, staying on top of everything is an impossible task.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mood things have been fine, I suppose. Up and down, as is to be expected, but overall nothing too terrible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have a job interview that&amp;rsquo;s sort of happening in the background. It&amp;rsquo;s been long and drawn-out over weeks at this point, which is&amp;hellip; not ideal, but it is what it is. It&amp;rsquo;s for dev work, which would be nice to get back into. I&amp;rsquo;m somewhere between apathetic at More Job Stuff, and cautiously optimistic that it could actually be great. So it goes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope your week&amp;rsquo;s been good so far. Thanks for reading.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Ladybunne&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloudy Monday</title>
      <link>https://ladybunne.net/cloudy-monday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 17:18:15 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ladybunne.net/cloudy-monday/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s a pretty cloudy Monday today. I had a property valuation this morning - a valuer came out to take some pictures of my apartment. I&amp;rsquo;m hoping this doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean my landlord is intending to sell, because that would mean I&amp;rsquo;d have to move out, and I &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; don&amp;rsquo;t want to do that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But it was otherwise painless! My vacuum broke about half an hour before the valuer arrived, which was a hassle. I&amp;rsquo;ll have to see if I can put it back together at some point.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking a lot about what sorts of things I want to write here. I&amp;rsquo;ve set myself two rules - be honest, and no deleting. That&amp;rsquo;s hard, because I don&amp;rsquo;t really want to leave a public trail of things that anyone can just come and learn about me&amp;hellip; but, maybe I should be less afraid of that. I think the alternative is kind of sad - who wants to look back and see 30 years of deleted memories?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, here I am. Trying to use this site to be a bit more outspoken about myself. I&amp;rsquo;m intentionally using this instead of, say, Twitter or another algorithm-riddled site. It&amp;rsquo;s a bit more &amp;ldquo;pure&amp;rdquo;, and less engineered to grab/hold attention. This is just me expressing myself&amp;hellip; shouting into the void and seeing what happens.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ll likely work on the format of this over time. I used to have a site that had both &amp;ldquo;posts&amp;rdquo; (long-form blog posts like this one) and &amp;ldquo;microposts&amp;rdquo; (like tweets but not on Twitter), and that worked well. I&amp;rsquo;ll see if I get around to adding that functionality in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Otherwise, we&amp;rsquo;ll see how this whole site thing holds up. Fingers crossed it works out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Ladybunne&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro</title>
      <link>https://ladybunne.net/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 21:12:29 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ladybunne.net/intro/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi. I&amp;rsquo;m Ladybunne, and this is my site. I&amp;rsquo;ve been meaning to remake this for quite some time. Sorry it&amp;rsquo;s taken so long.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope I didn&amp;rsquo;t keep you waiting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t have much to say right now. I need to set the site up and get it working properly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Talk to you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Ladybunne&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
